Ԑbᴐ -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
bosome -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
no -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
da -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
a -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
εtᴐ -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
so -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
11 -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
wᴐ -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
2023 -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
mu -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
εyε -X- _ O
Dwoada -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Denkyira -X- _ B-LOC
Akuropᴐn -X- _ I-LOC
mpanimfoᴐ -X- _ O
n -X- _ O
wᴐn -X- _ O
manfoᴐ -X- _ O
kaa -X- _ O
wᴐn -X- _ O
ti -X- _ O
famm -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
de -X- _ O
Owura -X- _ B-PER
James -X- _ I-PER
Alfred -X- _ I-PER
Bafu -X- _ I-PER
sii -X- _ O
ahennwa -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
sε -X- _ O
wᴐn -X- _ O
hene -X- _ O
foforᴐ -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Akuropᴐn -X- _ B-LOC
Ahennwa -X- _ B-MISC
no -X- _ O
hyε -X- _ O
Kyerεmfεm -X- _ O
anaa -X- _ O
Nifa -X- _ B-ORG
nkyekyεmu -X- _ I-ORG
kuo -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ase -X- _ O
wᴐ -X- _ O
Denkyira -X- _ B-LOC
Ahensεm -X- _ B-MISC
ne -X- _ O
wᴐn -X- _ O
Ahennie -X- _ B-ORG
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Akuropᴐn -X- _ B-ORG
Ahenwa -X- _ I-ORG
no -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
adehyeε -X- _ O
yε -X- _ O
Asakyirifoᴐ -X- _ B-ORG
a -X- _ O
wᴐfiri -X- _ O
Asakyiri -X- _ B-ORG
abusua -X- _ I-ORG
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wᴐagyinaa -X- _ O
sε -X- _ O
akofoᴐ -X- _ B-MISC
akokoᴐdurufo -X- _ I-MISC
a -X- _ O
wᴐn -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
yε -X- _ O
hu -X- _ O
wᴐ -X- _ O
Bankam -X- _ B-ORG
Dwa -X- _ I-ORG
Kεseε -X- _ I-ORG
a -X- _ O
εwᴐ -X- _ O
Denkyira -X- _ B-LOC
no -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Afe -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
1820 -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
mu -X- _ O
hᴐ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ᴐdεεfoᴐ -X- _ O
Kwadwo -X- _ B-PER
Tsibo -X- _ I-PER
a -X- _ O
ᴐyε -X- _ O
Denkyira -X- _ B-LOC
hene -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ᴐtᴐ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
15 -X- _ O
dii -X- _ O
Denkyirafoᴐ -X- _ B-MISC
anim -X- _ O
maa -X- _ O
wᴐfirii -X- _ O
baabi -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wᴐte -X- _ O
dada -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
twaa -X- _ O
Asuo -X- _ B-LOC
Ↄffin -X- _ I-LOC
sane -X- _ O
kᴐkyekyeree -X- _ O
Denkyiraman -X- _ B-MISC
wᴐ -X- _ O
hᴐ -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ↄde -X- _ O
Asraafokuo -X- _ B-ORG
ne -X- _ O
Akofokuo -X- _ B-ORG
binom -X- _ O
tete -X- _ O
sε -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Nifa -X- _ B-ORG
, -X- _ O
Adᴐnten -X- _ B-ORG
, -X- _ O
Benkum -X- _ B-ORG
ne -X- _ O
deε -X- _ O
εkeka -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
sisiii -X- _ O
Ↄffin -X- _ B-LOC
ano -X- _ O
sε -X- _ O
sε -X- _ O
aman -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ᴐtan -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
wᴐne -X- _ O
wᴐn -X- _ O
ntam -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
bi -X- _ O
rebεto -X- _ O
ahyε -X- _ O
wᴐn -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wᴐabᴐ -X- _ O
wᴐn -X- _ O
man -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
ban -X- _ O
afiri -X- _ O
saa -X- _ O
ntonhyεsoᴐ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ԑyε -X- _ O
Ahennwa -X- _ B-MISC
a -X- _ O
wᴐnya -X- _ O
firii -X- _ O
ᴐsa -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
εyε -X- _ O
Denkyira -X- _ B-LOC
nkonnwa -X- _ B-MISC
atitire -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
baako -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Nana -X- _ B-PER
Kofi -X- _ I-PER
Wiah -X- _ I-PER
II -X- _ I-PER
nyaa -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
mfitiaseε -X- _ O
sukuu -X- _ O
nteteeε -X- _ O
wᴐ -X- _ O
Akuropᴐn -X- _ B-ORG
Methodist -X- _ I-ORG
Primary -X- _ I-ORG
D. -X- _ I-ORG
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ᴐgyee -X- _ O
ntoasoᴐ -X- _ O
sukuu -X- _ O
nteteeε -X- _ O
wᴐ -X- _ O
Dunkwa -X- _ B-ORG
Junior -X- _ I-ORG
Secendary -X- _ I-ORG
School -X- _ I-ORG
. -X- _ O

St. -X- _ B-ORG
John’s -X- _ I-ORG
School -X- _ I-ORG
mu -X- _ O
wᴐ -X- _ O
Sekune -X- _ B-LOC
. -X- _ O

Akyire -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ᴐsane -X- _ O
yεε -X- _ O
Bachelor -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Commerce -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
B.com -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
wᴐ -X- _ O
Oguaa -X- _ B-ORG
Suapᴐn -X- _ I-ORG
( -X- _ O
University -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Cape -X- _ O
Coast -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ᴐde -X- _ O
adesua -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
gyinabea -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
εyε -X- _ O
fε -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
εsᴐ -X- _ O
ani -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
εwieeε -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ↄyε -X- _ O
sika -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
hwεfoᴐ -X- _ O
wᴐ -X- _ O
Chartered -X- _ B-ORG
Acountants -X- _ I-ORG
Ghana -X- _ I-ORG
Adesuabea -X- _ I-ORG
. -X- _ O

Nana -X- _ B-PER
Kofi -X- _ I-PER
II -X- _ I-PER
yε -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ᴐwa -X- _ O
anisoadehunu -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ᴐne -X- _ O
nnwumakuo -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
atwa -X- _ O
ahyia -X- _ O
Ghanaman -X- _ B-LOC
mu -X- _ O
ha -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
pii -X- _ O
ayε -X- _ O
adwuma -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Mprempren -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
yi -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ᴐno -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Sika -X- _ B-MISC
so -X- _ I-MISC
Difoᴐ -X- _ I-MISC
wᴐ -X- _ O
Opportunity -X- _ B-ORG
International -X- _ I-ORG
Savings -X- _ I-ORG
and -X- _ I-ORG
Loans -X- _ I-ORG
. -X- _ O

Wadi -X- _ O
dwuma -X- _ O
sε -X- _ O
Panin -X- _ B-MISC
a -X- _ I-MISC
ᴐhwε -X- _ O
toto -X- _ I-MISC
Sikasεm -X- _ I-MISC
wᴐ -X- _ O
Toyota -X- _ B-ORG
Ghana -X- _ I-ORG
Ltd -X- _ I-ORG
, -X- _ O
εnna -X- _ O
wasane -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
dwuma -X- _ O
sε -X- _ O
Sika -X- _ B-MISC
Korafoᴐ -X- _ I-MISC
wᴐ -X- _ O
Mobile -X- _ B-ORG
Ghana -X- _ I-ORG
Ltd -X- _ I-ORG
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wasane -X- _ O
ayε -X- _ O
Sika -X- _ B-MISC
mu -X- _ I-MISC
Nhwehwεmuyεfoᴐ -X- _ I-MISC
ne -X- _ O
Samufoᴐ -X- _ B-MISC
wᴐ -X- _ O
Coopers -X- _ B-ORG
and -X- _ I-ORG
Lybrand -X- _ I-ORG
. -X- _ O

Animdefoᴐ -X- _ O
atitire -X- _ O
binom -X- _ O
tete -X- _ O
sε -X- _ O
Denkyira -X- _ B-LOC
Atifido -X- _ I-LOC
fam -X- _ O
Apueeε -X- _ B-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
bi -X- _ O
te -X- _ O
sε -X- _ O
Onimuonyamfoᴐ -X- _ O
Festus -X- _ B-PER
Awuah -X- _ I-PER
Kofi -X- _ I-PER
, -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ᴐyε -X- _ O
Mansini -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
Ananmusini -X- _ B-MISC
wᴐ -X- _ O
Mmarahyεbadwam -X- _ B-ORG
, -X- _ O
Onimuonyamfoᴐ -X- _ O
Nana -X- _ B-PER
Amoako -X- _ I-PER
, -X- _ O
Mansini -X- _ B-MISC
no -X- _ O
ananmusini -X- _ B-MISC
wᴐ -X- _ O
Mmarahyεbadwan -X- _ B-ORG
a -X- _ O
watwa -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Denkyira -X- _ B-ORG
Development -X- _ I-ORG
Association -X- _ I-ORG
ne -X- _ O
Denkyira -X- _ B-ORG
Heritage -X- _ I-ORG
Foundation -X- _ I-ORG
mu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
atitire -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Yεsrε -X- _ O
Nyankopᴐn -X- _ B-PER
ne -X- _ O
Nananom -X- _ B-PER
sε -X- _ O
wᴐmma -X- _ O
n’ahennie -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
nyε -X- _ O
prᴐmprᴐm -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ᴐnni -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
nkwa -X- _ O
nna -X- _ O
mmee -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
n’ahennie -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
nyε -X- _ O
asomdwoeε -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
εnam -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
ama -X- _ O
Denkyira -X- _ B-LOC
Akuropᴐn -X- _ B-MISC
ne -X- _ O
Denkyiraman -X- _ B-MISC
nyinaa -X- _ O
ayε -X- _ O
kεse -X- _ O
bio -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
afa -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
ntoma -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
afira -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Owura -X- _ O
Akwasi -X- _ B-PER
Boadi -X- _ I-PER
Akrobeto -X- _ I-PER
yɛ -X- _ O
onipa -X- _ O
bi -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
n’abrabɔm -X- _ O
nsɛm -X- _ O
hyɛ -X- _ O
yɛn -X- _ O
nkuran -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Sɛdeɛ -X- _ O
mpanimfoɔ -X- _ O
ka -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
‘Ɔsoro -X- _ O
boa -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
ɔboa -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
ho’ -X- _ O
ɛnna -X- _ O
aburuburo -X- _ O
nkosua -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
adeɛ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛbɛyɛ -X- _ O
yie -X- _ O
nsɛe -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Wɔwoo -X- _ O
Owura -X- _ B-PER
Akwasi -X- _ I-PER
Boadi -X- _ I-PER
Obubuo -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
18 -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
, -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
1962 -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
wɔ -X- _ O
Asante -X- _ B-LOC
mantam -X- _ I-LOC
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɔfiri -X- _ O
Ayirebi -X- _ B-LOC
a -X- _ O
ɛwɔ -X- _ O
Akyem -X- _ B-LOC
Ɔda -X- _ I-LOC
wɔ -X- _ O
Atɔeɛ -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɔhyɛɛ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
sukuu -X- _ O
ase -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Akyem -X- _ B-ORG
Ayerebi -X- _ I-ORG
L/A -X- _ I-ORG
Mfitiaseɛ -X- _ I-ORG
ne -X- _ I-ORG
Adantam -X- _ I-ORG
sukuu -X- _ I-ORG
mu -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɛnna -X- _ O
ɔwiee -X- _ O
afe -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
1979 -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛwom -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wantumi -X- _ O
antwa -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
sɔhwɛ -X- _ O
ankɔ -X- _ O
sukuu -X- _ O
annuru -X- _ O
akyire -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nanso -X- _ O
ɔde -X- _ O
n’abrabɔ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
n’adwumaden -X- _ O
akyerɛ -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɛnyɛ -X- _ O
sukuu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
nwomasua -X- _ O
nko -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ɛma -X- _ O
onipa -X- _ O
di -X- _ O
yie -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
asetenam -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Akrobeto -X- _ B-PER
hyɛɛ -X- _ O
n’adwuma -X- _ O
ase -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
nsɛnkwaayini -X- _ O
mfeɛ -X- _ O
pii -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
atwam -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɔne -X- _ O
Kristo -X- _ B-ORG
Asafo -X- _ I-ORG
ahwɛgroɔ -X- _ I-ORG
kuo -X- _ I-ORG
a -X- _ O
Onimuonyamfoɔ -X- _ O
Kwadwo -X- _ B-PER
Safo -X- _ I-PER
Kantanka -X- _ I-PER
teeɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
bɔɔ -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
yɛɛ -X- _ O
adwuma -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Nnipa -X- _ O
binom -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
Akrobeto -X- _ B-PER
ne -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
dii -X- _ O
dwuma -X- _ O
saa -X- _ O
berɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Agya -X- _ B-PER
Koo -X- _ I-PER
, -X- _ O
Mercy -X- _ B-PER
Asiedu -X- _ I-PER
( -X- _ O
Asaabea -X- _ B-PER
) -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Nkɔmmɔdɛ -X- _ B-PER
. -X- _ I-PER

Ɛsiane -X- _ O
adwumaden -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ahofama -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ahobrɛaseɛ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
nteteɛ -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
Kristo -X- _ B-ORG
Asafo -X- _ I-ORG
de -X- _ O
maa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
nti -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Akrobeto -X- _ B-PER
dwumadie -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
sinitwani -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
bɛtuu -X- _ O
mpɔn -X- _ O
maa -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
ani -X- _ O
bɛgyee -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛnnɛ -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
, -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
yɛrebu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
dwumadie -X- _ O
sɔ -X- _ O
ani -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔagye -X- _ O
din -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
sinitwa -X- _ O
adwuma -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Akrobeto -X- _ B-PER
da -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
fua -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɔka -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔaboa -X- _ O
ama -X- _ O
Kumase -X- _ B-ORG
Sinitwa -X- _ I-ORG
kuo -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
atumi -X- _ O
agye -X- _ O
nhini -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛde -X- _ O
rebɛsi -X- _ O
ɛnnɛ -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
yi -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wɔtwa -X- _ O
sini -X- _ O
bi -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
Akrobeto -X- _ B-PER
nka -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
dodoɔ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
ani -X- _ O
nnye -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wɔbɛhwɛ -X- _ O
sini -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ɛfiri -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wayɛ -X- _ O
Ahoampamu -X- _ O
gyeene -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
sinitwa -X- _ O
adwuma -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛhɔ -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɔdanee -X- _ O
n’adwuma -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
sinitwani -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
bɛyɛɛ -X- _ O
obi -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɔkenkan -X- _ O
kaseɛbɔ -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
TV -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Nokwasɛm -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
onipa -X- _ O
biara -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɔnim -X- _ O
Akrobeto -X- _ B-PER
yie -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
bɛgye -X- _ O
atom -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɛfiri -X- _ O
tete -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
de -X- _ O
bɛsi -X- _ O
ɛnnɛ -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
yi -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
dwumadie -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
yɛ -X- _ O
anika -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
onipa -X- _ O
biara -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
ani -X- _ O
gye -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛwom -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
Akrobeto -X- _ B-PER
nni -X- _ O
abodin -X- _ O
krataa -X- _ O
anaasɛ -X- _ O
wantumi -X- _ O
ankɔ -X- _ O
sukuu -X- _ O
annuru -X- _ O
akyire -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nanso -X- _ O
wabɛyɛ -X- _ O
kokurommoti -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
yɛnsane -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
mmɔ -X- _ O
pɔ -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
sinitwa -X- _ O
adwuma -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛnnɛ -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
, -X- _ O
n’akatua -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɔgye -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
mpo -X- _ O
boro -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
binom -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔakɔ -X- _ O
sukuu -X- _ O
aduru -X- _ O
akyire -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
bebree -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛba -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
din -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wagye -X- _ O
bi -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
wiase -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛfiri -X- _ O
berɛ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɔhyɛɛ -X- _ O
aseɛ -X- _ O
kenkann -X- _ O
kaseɛbɔ -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
UTV -X- _ B-ORG
so -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
aborɔfo -X- _ O
binom -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔmfiri -X- _ O
Abibirem -X- _ B-LOC
mpo -X- _ O
akyerɛ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
mmɔdemmɔ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
anisɔ -X- _ O
kɛseɛ -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Wɔde -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
sereɛ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
kasa -X- _ O
mpo -X- _ O
ahyehyɛ -X- _ O
sini -X- _ O
ahodoɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔde -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
nsɛnkwaa -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Yei -X- _ O
kyerɛ -X- _ O
sɛdeɛ -X- _ O
wiase -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
akyerɛ -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ani -X- _ O
gye -X- _ O
n’hofama -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
mmɔdemmɔ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Sika -X- _ B-MISC
nso -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wanya -X- _ O
bebree -X- _ O
kwa -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Yɛhwɛ -X- _ O
sɛdeɛ -X- _ O
Akrobeto -X- _ B-PER
de -X- _ O
n’adom -X- _ O
akyɛdeɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
n’ahoɔden -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
n’ahofama -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
mmɔdemmɔ -X- _ O
atumi -X- _ O
ayɛ -X- _ O
nnepa -X- _ O
pii -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
asetenam -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
berɛ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
nwomasua -X- _ O
anaa -X- _ O
abodin -X- _ O
biara -X- _ O
nka -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɛma -X- _ O
yɛhunu -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
biribiara -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
yɛbɔ -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
mmɔden -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
asetenam -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɛsɛ -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
yɛyere -X- _ O
yɛn -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
yɛyɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
yie -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Azuma -X- _ B-PER
Nelson -X- _ I-PER
yɛ -X- _ O
akuturukubɔni -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wiase -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
nim -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
yie -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Azuma -X- _ B-PER
yɛ -X- _ O
Ghanani -X- _ B-MISC
a -X- _ O
wɔwoo -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
Kitawonsa -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
19 -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
, -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
1958 -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
mu -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Nkran -X- _ B-LOC
. -X- _ O

N’awofoɔ -X- _ O
mma -X- _ O
nwɔtwe -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Azuma -X- _ B-PER
ne -X- _ O
kaakyire -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
biribi -X- _ O
nhyɛ -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
nni -X- _ O
n’awofoɔ -X- _ O
nsam -X- _ O
saa -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Afe -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
1978 -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɔkɔsii -X- _ O
akan -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Abibiman -X- _ B-LOC
Nyinaa -X- _ O
agokansie -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Kɔmɔnwɛlt -X- _ B-ORG
agokansie -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Akansie -X- _ O
mmienu -X- _ O
yinom -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Azuma -X- _ B-PER
nyaa -X- _ O
sika -X- _ B-MISC
kɔkɔɔ -X- _ I-MISC
abasobɔdeɛ -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Azuma -X- _ B-PER
sii -X- _ O
akuturukubɔ -X- _ O
akansie -X- _ O
ahodoɔ -X- _ O
13 -X- _ O
dii -X- _ O
nkunim -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
berɛ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɔfirii -X- _ O
akuturukubɔ -X- _ O
ase -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Afe -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
1980 -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɔne -X- _ O
Ɛngresi -X- _ O
akuturukubɔni -X- _ O
Jeff -X- _ B-PER
Thomas -X- _ I-PER
sii -X- _ O
akan -X- _ O
maa -X- _ O
Azuma -X- _ B-PER
dii -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
nkunim -X- _ O
bɛgyee -X- _ O
abodin -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔfrɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
British -X- _ B-MISC
Kɔmɔnwɛlt -X- _ I-MISC
Fɛdaweit -X- _ I-MISC
. -X- _ I-MISC

Saa -X- _ O
nkunimdie -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
buee -X- _ O
kwan -X- _ O
maa -X- _ O
wiase -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
hunuu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
mmɔdemmɔ -X- _ O
nti -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔfirii -X- _ O
aseɛ -X- _ O
buu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
okunini -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
akuturukubɔfoɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔsi -X- _ O
akan -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Fɛdaweit -X- _ B-MISC
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
wiase -X- _ O
baabiara -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

1981 -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Azuma -X- _ B-PER
buu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
kɛtɛ -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
kɔpuee -X- _ O
Amerika -X- _ B-LOC
ne -X- _ O
ɔpanin -X- _ O
bi -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔfrɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
Don -X- _ B-PER
King -X- _ I-PER
kɔyɛɛ -X- _ O
adwuma -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

1982 -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Azuma -X- _ B-PER
ne -X- _ O
akuturukubɔni -X- _ O
Salvador -X- _ B-PER
Sanchez -X- _ I-PER
de -X- _ O
bɔɔ -X- _ O
ani -X- _ O
maa -X- _ O
Azuma -X- _ B-PER
boroo -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
pasaa -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɔbɛgyee -X- _ O
saa -X- _ O
abodin -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
akyi -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɔsii -X- _ O
akan -X- _ O
mpɛn -X- _ O
nwɔtwe -X- _ O
dii -X- _ O
nkunim -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
bɔɔ -X- _ O
n’abodin -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
ban -X- _ O
ansa -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
akyire -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
akuturukubɔni -X- _ O
Wilfredo -X- _ B-PER
Gomez -X- _ I-PER
rebɛgye -X- _ O
afiri -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
nsam -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
1984 -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɔbɛgyee -X- _ O
saa -X- _ O
abodin -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɔsii -X- _ O
akan -X- _ O
mpɛn -X- _ O
nnan -X- _ O
dii -X- _ O
nkunim -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
de -X- _ O
bɔɔ -X- _ O
n’abodin -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
ban -X- _ O
kɔsii -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
akuturukubɔni -X- _ O
bi -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔfrɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
Genaro -X- _ B-PER
Hernandez -X- _ I-PER
bɛgye -X- _ O
firii -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
nsam -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
1988 -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɔde -X- _ O
n’akuturukubɔ -X- _ O
akansie -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
baa -X- _ O
awieeɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wako -X- _ O
ntɔkwa -X- _ O
ahoroɔ -X- _ O
47 -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
nkunim -X- _ O
39 -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɛnna -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wadi -X- _ O
ntwo -X- _ O
6 -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Mpanimfoɔ -X- _ O
se -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
‘Kuntunu -X- _ O
hwan -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
n’akyi -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ɛkɔ’ -X- _ O
nti -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
berɛ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
Azuma -X- _ B-PER
de -X- _ O
n’adwuma -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
akuturukubɔni -X- _ O
baa -X- _ O
awieeɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɔsane -X- _ O
baa -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ B-LOC
bɛbuee -X- _ O
beaeɛ -X- _ O
bi -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔde -X- _ O
tete -X- _ O
akuturukubɔfoɔ -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ɔman -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Bio -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɔdi -X- _ O
dwuma -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
ofutufoɔ -X- _ B-MISC
ma -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ B-ORG
aban -X- _ I-ORG
no -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
akuturukubɔ -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
nsɛm -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛde -X- _ O
bɛsi -X- _ O
ɛnnɛ -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
nyinaa -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɛsiane -X- _ O
akokoɔduro -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
adwumaden -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
nsi -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
Azuma -X- _ B-PER
Nelson -X- _ I-PER
daa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
nti -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔbu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
akuturukubɔfoɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
adwuma -X- _ O
sɔɔ -X- _ O
ani -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Afrika -X- _ B-LOC
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
baako -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
wiase -X- _ O
baabiara -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ebia -X- _ O
yɛbɛsua -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
nti -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛte -X- _ O
saa -X- _ O
akyire -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Sɛdeɛ -X- _ O
Akanfoɔ -X- _ B-MISC
frɛ -X- _ O
nnapɔnna -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛsisi -X- _ O
nna -X- _ O
nsia -X- _ O
yinom -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ɛdidi -X- _ O
soɔ -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
: -X- _ O
Akanman -X- _ B-ORG
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
bɔne -X- _ O
biara -X- _ O
tɔ -X- _ O
adaduanan -X- _ B-DATE
akyi -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛduru -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
bɔne -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Akanfoɔ -X- _ B-MISC
nyɛ -X- _ O
adwuma -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Mmom -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔtena -X- _ O
fie -X- _ O
ma -X- _ O
nkonnwa -X- _ B-MISC
, -X- _ O
nananom -X- _ B-PER
abosom -X- _ I-PER
ne -X- _ O
nsamanfoɔ -X- _ B-MISC
no -X- _ O
aduane -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Saa -X- _ O
nna -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
biara -X- _ O
yɛ -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
kronkrkon -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔntoto -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ase -X- _ O
koraa -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛwom -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
Akanfoɔ -X- _ B-MISC
ntoto -X- _ O
nnapɔnna -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
biara -X- _ O
ase -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nanso -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ani -X- _ O
ku -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Akwasidɛɛ -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
. -X- _ O

Sɛdeɛ -X- _ O
Asantefoɔ -X- _ B-MISC
amammerɛ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
abakɔsɛm -X- _ O
kyerɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
titire -X- _ O
binom -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔde -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
nkwa -X- _ O
too -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
nsam -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
de -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ti -X- _ O
ko -X- _ O
gyee -X- _ O
akyerɛma -X- _ O
maa -X- _ O
Asanteman -X- _ B-MISC
. -X- _ O

Saa -X- _ O
ahemfo -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ahemmaa -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
titire -X- _ O
yinom -X- _ O
atuhoama -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
akokoɔduro -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
som -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
nokorɛdie -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
dɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔnya -X- _ O
maa -X- _ O
Asanteman -X- _ B-MISC
nti -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔtumi -X- _ O
dii -X- _ O
ako -X- _ O
bɔɔ -X- _ O
Sika -X- _ B-MISC
Dwa -X- _ I-MISC
ho -X- _ O
ban -X- _ O
maa -X- _ O
Asanteman -X- _ B-MISC
nyaa -X- _ O
n’asomdwoe -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
n’animuonyam -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Yei -X- _ O
nti -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
atirimpɔ -X- _ O
titire -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
Asantefoɔ -X- _ B-MISC
de -X- _ O
hyɛ -X- _ O
Adɛɛ -X- _ B-MISC
Kɛseɛ -X- _ I-MISC
fa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔbɛkae -X- _ O
dɔmmarima -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
mmaa -X- _ O
akokoɔdurufoɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔde -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
nkwa -X- _ O
bɔɔ -X- _ O
afɔreɛ -X- _ O
maa -X- _ O
Asanteman -X- _ B-MISC
no -X- _ O
ɛfiri -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
onipa -X- _ O
yɛ -X- _ O
adeɛ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɔsɛ -X- _ O
ayeyie -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Mpanimfoɔ -X- _ B-PER
se -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
“Deɛ -X- _ O
waturu -X- _ O
wo -X- _ O
akɔhwɛ -X- _ O
nkwa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
yɛnturu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
nkɔhwɛ -X- _ O
owuo -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Saa -X- _ O
berɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔgu -X- _ O
nsa -X- _ O
frɛ -X- _ O
saman -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
biara -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɔfata -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wɔto -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
badin -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Akanman -X- _ B-MISC
mu -X- _ O
sane -X- _ O
ma -X- _ O
nananom -X- _ B-PER
abosom -X- _ I-PER
ne -X- _ O
nsamanfoɔ -X- _ B-PER
no -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
aduane -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

