-DOCSTART- -X- O
Korɔbea -X- _ B-ORG
Asante -X- _ I-ORG
Kɔtɔkɔ -X- _ I-ORG
yɛ -X- _ O
ɔman -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔayɛ -X- _ O
kokuromoti -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
yɛnsan -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
mmɔ -X- _ O
pɔ -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ B-LOC
. -X- _ O

Abakɔsɛm -X- _ O
mpo -X- _ O
kyerɛ -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Asantefoɔ -X- _ B-MISC
nyaa -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
faahodie -X- _ O
1935 -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
ansa -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ B-LOC
renya -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
1957 -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛrekame -X- _ O
ayɛ -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Asantefoɔ -X- _ B-MISC
agye -X- _ O
din -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ B-LOC
abakɔsɛm -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
wiase -X- _ O
afaanan -X- _ O
baabiara -X- _ O
kyɛn -X- _ O
kasakuo -X- _ B-ORG
ahodoɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛwɔ -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Yei -X- _ O
nti -X- _ O
ɛnnɛ -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
, -X- _ O
yɛrebɛsua -X- _ O
biribi -X- _ O
kakra -X- _ O
afa -X- _ O
Asanteman -X- _ B-MISC
abakɔsɛm -X- _ O
ho.Ansa -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
Anɔkye -X- _ B-PER
Frimpɔn -X- _ I-PER
Kɔtɔbere -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔnim -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
Ɔkɔmfo -X- _ B-PER
Anɔkye -X- _ I-PER
regye -X- _ O
Sika -X- _ B-MISC
dwa -X- _ I-MISC
Kofi -X- _ B-PER
afiri -X- _ O
Tweaduampɔn -X- _ B-LOC
hɔ -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ahemfo -X- _ O
binom -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
Asanteman -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
dada -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Saa -X- _ O
ahemfo -X- _ O
yinom -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Nananom -X- _ O
Twum -X- _ B-PER
ne -X- _ O
Antwi -X- _ B-PER
, -X- _ O
Nana -X- _ O
Korɔbea -X- _ B-PER
Amamfi -X- _ I-PER
, -X- _ O
Nana -X- _ O
Oti -X- _ B-PER
Akɛntɛn -X- _ I-PER
, -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Nana -X- _ O
Obiri -X- _ B-PER
Yɛboa.Deɛ -X- _ I-PER
ɛteɛ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
yɛreka -X- _ O
atumfoɔ -X- _ O
dunsia -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔasom -X- _ O
Sika -X- _ O
dwa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
atumfoɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
yɛabobɔ -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
din -X- _ O
yinom -X- _ O
nka -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Mmom -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɛhyɛ -X- _ O
aseɛ -X- _ O
firi -X- _ O
Otumfoɔ -X- _ O
Ɔsɛe -X- _ B-PER
Tutu -X- _ I-PER
I -X- _ I-PER
so -X- _ O
ɛfiri -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
pɛn -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
Ɔkɔmfo -X- _ B-PER
Anɔkye -X- _ I-PER
yii -X- _ O
Sika -X- _ O
dwa -X- _ O
Kofi -X- _ B-PER
maa -X- _ O
Asanteman.Yei -X- _ O
nti -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
yɛrebɛbobɔ -X- _ O
atumfoɔ -X- _ O
16 -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
nyinaa -X- _ O
din -X- _ O
nnidisoɔ -X- _ O
nnidisoɔ -X- _ O
afiri -X- _ O
berɛ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
Asanteman -X- _ O
nyaa -X- _ O
Sika -X- _ O
dwa -X- _ O
abɛsi -X- _ O
Otumfoɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɔtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
dunsia -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Yei -X- _ O
kyerɛ -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
yɛn -X- _ O
sikasɛm -X- _ O
nhyɛ -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
nkɔ -X- _ O
yie -X- _ O
saa.Nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
bi -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔyɛ -X- _ O
faa -X- _ O
amantam -X- _ O
ahodoɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
hia -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ B-LOC
ha -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
ada -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɛwom -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ LOC
sikasɛm -X- _ O
nhyɛ -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
nkɔ -X- _ O
yie -X- _ O
saa -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nanso -X- _ O
ɛsono -X- _ O
sɛdeɛ -X- _ O
ahokyerɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
teɛ -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
mantam -X- _ O
biara -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Nanso -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
woanhwɛ -X- _ O
yie -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
ɛfiri -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
yɛbɛka -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
asɛm -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
baeɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
bɛma -X- _ O
wo -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
adwiri -X- _ O
wo.Wɔgyinaa -X- _ O
mfeɛ -X- _ B-DATE/TIME
2010 -X- _ I-DATE/TIME
nnipa -X- _ O
dodoɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔkan -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ B-PER
no -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔyɛɛ -X- _ O
saa -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛsiane -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wɔyɛɛ -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
ansa -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔrebɛte -X- _ O
amantam -X- _ O
afoforɔ -X- _ O
aka -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ɛwɔ -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
dada -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
nti -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔde -X- _ O
amantan -X- _ O
dada -X- _ O
du -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ɛdii -X- _ O
dwuma.Nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
baa -X- _ O
awieeɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
sɛdeɛ -X- _ O
ɛbɛdaa -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
amantam -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
hia -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
kɔpem -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
hia -X- _ O
ano -X- _ O
nyɛ -X- _ O
den -X- _ O
ahe -X- _ O
biara -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ B-LOC
no -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ɛdidi -X- _ O
soɔ -X- _ O
yi.Atifi -X- _ B-LOC
Atɔeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
muMantam -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
daa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
kan -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
buruburoo -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔyɛɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ B-LOC
no -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Atifi -X- _ B-LOC
Atɔeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Saa -X- _ O
mantam -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɔmansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛmu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Wa -X- _ B-LOC
Atɔeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛmu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
92.4 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
kyerɛɛ -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
buruburoo.Wa -X- _ B-LOC
Apueeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmienu -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ahokyerɛ -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
Atifi -X- _ B-LOC
Atɔeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɔmansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmiɛnsa -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛmu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Atifi -X- _ B-LOC
Atɔeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Sissala -X- _ B-LOC
Atɔeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
mansini -X- _ I-LOC
a -X- _ O
ɛmu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
81.2 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ɛbɛdaa -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
buruburoo -X- _ O
no.Atifi -X- _ B-LOC
Apueeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
muSaa -X- _ O
mantam -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
mantam -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
daa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmienu -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛmu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
di -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
buruburoo -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ B-LOC
. -X- _ O

Mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛdi -X- _ O
kan -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ahokyerɛ -X- _ O
buruburoo -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Builsa -X- _ B-LOC
Anaafoɔ -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
84.4 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Wɔn -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmienu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Bawku -X- _ B-LOC
Atɔeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
68.1 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmiɛnsa -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ahokyerɛ -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Atifi -X- _ B-LOC
Apueeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Bongo -X- _ B-LOC
mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
67.4 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛnna -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
nnan -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Nabdam -X- _ B-LOC
mansini -X- _ I-LOC
a -X- _ O
ɛmu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
63.0 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
daa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
buruburoo -X- _ O
no.Mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛbɛdaa -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
ɛmu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
nhyɛ -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
nni -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
buruburoo -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Kassena -X- _ B-LOC
Nankana -X- _ I-LOC
Atɔeeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛmu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
13.1 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
daa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
buruburoo.Atifi -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
muSɛdeɛ -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
daa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
yɛreka -X- _ O
amantam -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
hia -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Ghana -X- _ B-LOC
a -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Atifi -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmiɛnsa -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
kan -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛmu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
di -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
buruburoo -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Atifi -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
mu -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Apueeɛ -X- _ B-LOC
Fam -X- _ I-LOC
Gonja -X- _ I-LOC
( -X- _ O
84.2 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Wɔfiri -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
Bole -X- _ B-LOC
( -X- _ O
79.4 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
atoa -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Afei -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Kpandai -X- _ B-LOC
( -X- _ O
76.9 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
Mansini -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
ɛtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmiɛnsa -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛmu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
nhyɛ -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
nni -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
buruburoo -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Tamale -X- _ B-LOC
Mansini -X- _ O
no -X- _ I-LOC
. -X- _ O

Nanso -X- _ O
ɛhɔ -X- _ O
mpo -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
24.6 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
hɔ.Bono -X- _ B-LOC
Ahafo -X- _ I-LOC
Mantam -X- _ O
muBono -X- _ B-LOC
Ahafo -X- _ I-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
nnan -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ahokyerɛ -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔyɛeɛ -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Saa -X- _ O
mantam -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
daa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛdi -X- _ O
kan -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛmu -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Kintampo -X- _ B-LOC
Anaafoɔ -X- _ I-LOC
Fam -X- _ I-LOC
Manfini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mufoɔ -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
78.3 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Wɔn -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmienu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Banda -X- _ B-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mufoɔ -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
78.0 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
.Mansini -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
nhyɛ -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
nkyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
pii -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Bono -X- _ B-LOC
Ahafo -X- _ I-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
mu -X- _ O
sɛdeɛ -X- _ O
nhwehwɛnu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
daa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Dɔmaa -X- _ B-LOC
Atɔeɛ -X- _ I-LOC
Fam -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mufoɔ -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
9 -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

9 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
.Asante -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
muMantam -X- _ O
foforɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
daa -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
adi -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Asante -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛdi -X- _ O
kan -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Asante -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
mu -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
sɛdeɛ -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
kyerɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Sekyere -X- _ B-LOC
Afram -X- _ I-LOC
Plains -X- _ I-LOC
Atifi -X- _ I-LOC
Famfoɔ -X- _ O

Mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmienu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Edwira -X- _ B-LOC
Sekye -X- _ I-LOC
Dumasi -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Afei -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛtwa -X- _ O
toɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛmufoɔ -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
yie -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Asante -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
mu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Ahafo -X- _ B-LOC
Ano -X- _ I-LOC
Atifi -X- _ I-LOC
Famfoɔ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛhɔ -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
46.4 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
buruburoo.Ɛwom -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
amansini -X- _ O
ahodoɔ -X- _ O
binom -X- _ O
mufoɔ -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Asante -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
mu -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nanso -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ahokyerɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
nyɛ -X- _ O
nea -X- _ O
ano -X- _ O
yɛ -X- _ O
den -X- _ O
saa -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Saa -X- _ O
amansini -X- _ O
yinom -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Asɔkɔre -X- _ B-LOC
Mampong -X- _ I-LOC
( -X- _ O
3.3 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Afigya -X- _ B-LOC
Kwabre -X- _ I-LOC
( -X- _ O
4.0 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Atwima -X- _ B-LOC
Kwanwoma -X- _ I-LOC
( -X- _ O
4.9 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
.Apueeɛ -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
muApueeɛ -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
di -X- _ O
Asante -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
akyi -X- _ O
pɛɛ -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ahokyerɛ -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Yei -X- _ O
kyerɛ -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Apueeɛ -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
nsia -X- _ O
sɛdeɛ -X- _ O
nhyehyɛeɛ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
teɛ -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Saa -X- _ O
mantam -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔkyerɛ -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
yie -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Kwahu -X- _ B-LOC
Afram -X- _ I-LOC
Plains -X- _ I-LOC
Anaafoɔ -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
kyerɛ -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
hia -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
dodoɔ -X- _ O
bɛyɛ -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
59.7 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Afei -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmiɛnsa -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Atifi -X- _ B-LOC
Manya -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mufoɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
43.6 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
hɔ.Amansini -X- _ O
nnan -X- _ O
binom -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ɛwom -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
deɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nanso -X- _ O
ɛnyɛ -X- _ O
nea -X- _ O
ano -X- _ O
yɛ -X- _ O
den -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
nkaeɛ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
yɛabobɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Saa -X- _ O
amanini -X- _ O
nnan -X- _ O
yinom -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
: -X- _ O
New -X- _ B-LOC
Dwaben -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
4.6 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Dɛnkyɛmmoɔ -X- _ B-LOC
( -X- _ O
4.6 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Nsawam -X- _ B-LOC
Adoagyiri -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
( -X- _ O
6.3 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Suhum -X- _ B-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
( -X- _ O
6.5 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
.Frao -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
muFrao -X- _ I-LOC
mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
tɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
nson -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ahokyerɛ -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Wɔkyerɛ -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
baabi -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
ano -X- _ O
yɛ -X- _ O
den -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
saa -X- _ O
mantam -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Adaklu -X- _ B-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Wɔn -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmienu -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Kadjebi -X- _ B-LOC
mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mufoɔ -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Mansini -X- _ O
foforɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ohia -X- _ O
ano -X- _ O
yɛ -X- _ O
den -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
Frao -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Agotime -X- _ B-LOC
Ziope -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
ɛfiri -X- _ O
sɛ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
dodoɔ -X- _ O
bɛyɛ -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
62.1 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
.Mansini -X- _ O
foforɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
hia -X- _ O
nanso -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
hia -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
ano -X- _ O
nhyɛ -X- _ O
da -X- _ O
nyɛ -X- _ O
den -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Akatsi -X- _ B-LOC
Anaafoɔ -X- _ I-LOC
mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Nnipa -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
dodoɔ -X- _ O
bɛyɛ -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
10.5 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
pɛ.Nkran -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
muNkran -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
mantam -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
nwɔtwe -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
amantam -X- _ O
ahodoɔ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
hia -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
nhwehwɛmu -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Mansini -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛdi -X- _ O
kan -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
saa -X- _ O
mantam -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Shai -X- _ B-LOC
Osudoku -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Deɛ -X- _ O
ɛtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
mmienu -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Ningo -X- _ B-LOC
Prampram -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

La -X- _ B-LOC
Dade -X- _ I-LOC
Kotopon -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
sei -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
1.3 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔdi -X- _ O
hia -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
Nkran -X- _ B-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
nnipa -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
2.5 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
na -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
ho -X- _ O
kyere -X- _ O
wɔn -X- _ O
pa -X- _ O
ara -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Ɛnna -X- _ O
La -X- _ B-LOC
Nkwantanang -X- _ I-LOC
Madina -X- _ I-LOC
Mansini -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
nso -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
ahokyerɛ -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛwɔ -X- _ O
hɔ -X- _ O
no -X- _ O
yɛ -X- _ O
( -X- _ O
2.8 -X- _ O
% -X- _ O
) -X- _ O
.Mfimfini -X- _ O
Mantam -X- _ O
muMantam -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
ɛtɔ -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
nkron -X- _ O
wɔ -X- _ O
ahokyerɛ -X- _ O
yi -X- _ O
mu -X- _ O
ne -X- _ O
Mfimfini -X- _ B-LOC
Mantam -X- _ I-LOC
no -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

